www.aishwaryabagade.in

Aishwarya Bagade

UI UX Designer

DESIGN EXPERIENCE

UI UX | Ghar Ho Toh Aisa - Real Estate | Client Project

Dec 2023 - April 2024

Led the complete redesign of 'Ghar Ho Toh Aisa,' transforming their outdated real estate website into a modern, user-friendly platform. Introduced new features and enhanced user engagement and improve overall functionality.

UI UX | Dialable - Business Directory | Client Project

Jan 2024 - May 2024

Designed an accessible website for 'Dialable', a business directory platform catering for disabled users. Focused on enhancing user experience with accessibility in mind and usability for all users.

UI Design | Muse Gallery - Mobile App | Personal Project

Jan 2024 - March 2024

Designed an intuitive museum app and focused on enhancing user experience through seamless navigation and interactive elements.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Redux Solutions

Role: UI UX Designer

Dec 2023 - May 2024

Joined Redux Solutions in 2023, contributing to multiple projects to enhance user experience. My role involved creating intuitive and visually appealing designs to meet client needs.

GrayQuest Education Finance Pvt. Ltd

Role: Associate - Disbursement

Sep 2022 - Jan 2024

Joined GrayQuest in 2022 as an Associate -

Disbursement, managed loan applications/settlements.

Played a key role in collaboration and team management.

I am passionate and creative UI/UX designer with experience in freelance projects. Enthusiastic about visual design, creativity, and art, and eager to bring usercentric designs to life.

aishwaryaabagade3@gmail.com/+(91)8779612395

linkedin.com/in/aishwarya-bagade-0b0a92291

SKILLS

Design

Wireframing & Prototyping, User Research, Affinity
Diagrams, Visual Design, User Testing, Web Design,
Interaction Design, Style Guides, Responsive Design

Web Development

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, React, React-Bootstrap, Node.js

Soft Skills

Collaboration and Communication, Problem-Solving,
Attention to Detail, Project Management, Accessibility,
Adaptability, Interviewing

Tools

Figma, Adobe (XD, Illustrator, After Effects, Premiere Pro), Miro, InVision, Wireframe.cc, Notion, FigJam

EDUCATION

Google UX Design - Coursera

2023 - 2024

Web Development - Trycatch Institute

2022 - 2023

B.A Graduation(CGPA - 8.71) - Patkar Varde College

2019 - 2022

PERSONAL INTERESTS

Drawing & Painting, Design, Baking, Learning languages,

Travelling